http://www.peacebridge.com/index.php/about-us-sp-1874923374/privacy-policy

HomeAutos & Passenger Duty FreeE-ZPassID RequirementsLane ConfigurationNEXUSPeace Bridge AdvantagesPetsTips for CrossingTollsCBP Border Wait Time AppCommercial Customs BrokersDuty FreeE-ZPassFASTID RequirementsTollsTruck Loads/Special Loads ProgramSpecial Load ApplicationCBP Border Wait Time AppBicyclists Bike to the BridgeWalk the BridgeVendors Employment ApplicatonCanadian ApplicationUS ApplicationBoard Member OpportunityRequests for ProposalsRequests for QualificationsFull-Time OpportunitiesPart-Time OpportunitiesTerms and ConditionsEqual Employment Opportunity
Privacy Policy
HomeAutos & Passenger VehiclesDuty FreeE-ZPassID RequirementsLane ConfigurationNEXUSPeace Bridge AdvantagesPetsTips for CrossingTollsCBP Border Wait Time AppCommercial VehiclesCustoms BrokersDuty FreeE-ZPassFASTID RequirementsTollsTruck Loads/Special Loads ProgramSpecial Load ApplicationCBP Border Wait Time AppBicyclists & PedestriansBike to the BridgeWalk the BridgeVendors &
EmploymentEmployment ApplicatonCanadian ApplicationUS ApplicationBoard Member OpportunityRequests for ProposalsRequests for QualificationsFull-Time OpportunitiesPart-Time OpportunitiesTerms and ConditionsEqual Employment Opportunity
Privacy Policy
Commitment To Your Privacy
This site is owned and operated by the Buffalo and Fort Erie Public Bridge Authority. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. It is our goal to make your experience online satisfying and secure. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.
Information the Authority Gathers and Tracks
The Authority gathers two types of information about users:1.) Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions such as questions posed by web site viewers in the "Contact Us" section as well as questions answered by applicants on the Individual E-ZPass On-line Application. These are voluntary submissions to receive answers to individual questions and to sign up for an E-ZPass account.2.) Information the Authority gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our site. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help us better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does the Authority divulge any information about an individual user to a third party without the knowledge of the web site viewer.
The Authority Gathers User Information in the Following Process: Optional Voluntary Information
We offer the following service, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:
1.) On the "Contact Us" web page: Viewer's option to receive answers to their questions through a return e-mail response from the Authority or their tenants.
2.) Viewer's option to sign up for a Peace Bridge E-ZPass Individual Account on-line: Information voluntarily submitted may include name, contact information including address, credit card number(s), vehicle(s), license plate number(s), as well as other personal data.
Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.
Usage tracking on the www.peacebridge.com web site:
1.) The Authority tracks user traffic patterns throughout the site. However, we do not correlate this information with any data about individual users. The Authority does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).
Use of Information
The Authority uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our site, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our site users like and dislike based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to deliver better service to you.
Sharing of the Information
The Authority uses the above-described information to tailor the website content to suit your needs. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.
Security
The Authority operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.
Opt-Out Policy
We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices may include opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users.
Your Consent
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by the Authority. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
The
Peace Bridge
About UsAuthority InformationBoard of DirectorsOffice LocationPeace Bridge FactsPrivacy PolicyPublicationsRental SpaceService of ProcessStewardshipCommunity ProgramsBike to the BridgeBridge in BloomBridge in LightGame Day Travel TipsMewinzhaSponsorshipsStormwater ManagementHistorical Traffic StatisticsDaily VolumesMonthly VolumesYearly VolumesMedia RoomPress Releases & AdvisoriesDigital Display RequestsWeb Videos and EventsCDN WebcamsUS WebcamsPressContact Us
You are here:
Copyright © 2020.
Buffalo and Fort Erie Public Bridge Authority. All Rights Reserved.
Desktop Version
